ica.gov.ae 2019-11-30

# Privacy Policy - Federal Authority For Identity and Citizenship

### Privacy Pledge

Federal Authority for Identity and Citizenship is committed to protecting the privacy of Users at all times.

Emirates Identity only shares Customer Information and other Personally Identifiable Information with other government entities which are authorized by Federal Authority for Identity and Citizenship.

Federal Authority for Identity and Citizenship maintains security standards and procedures designed to protect Customer Information and other Personally Identifiable Information. It will continue to test and update its technology to improve ability to protect Customer Information and other Personally Identifiable Information.

### Consent to Use Information

By using any Product and/or by affirmatively accepting the License Agreement or this Privacy Policy, each User consents to the collection and use of all information that the User provides to Federal Authority for Identity and Citizenship, all information that is provided to Federal Authority for Identity and Citizenship on behalf of that User, and all information that Federal Authority for Identity and Citizenship collects based on that User's use of the ID cards, including, without limitation, all Information and other Personally Identifiable Information.

### Policies Regarding the Collection and disclosure of Information

Federal Authority for Identity and Citizenship collects personal information such as name, address, and email address, when user knowingly provides it to Federal Authority for Identity and Citizenship. In addition, Federal Authority for Identity and Citizenship may collect other information provided by users such as address, date of birth and other personally identifiable information, when user set up an online account or order service online. Federal Authority for Identity and Citizenship Web servers automatically collect statistical information about users visit such as pages visited and which browsers are used to visit our site. None of this information is associated with user as an individual (see information about cookies).

### Policies Regarding the Use and Disclosure of Information

Information Use and Sharing : Federal Authority for Identity and Citizenship may use and share the Customer Information and other Personally Identifiable Information that it collects among various departments within Federal Authority for Identity and Citizenship and its subsidiaries that perform functions such as servicing User accounts, preparing reports and other user activities.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small data string our server writes to your hard drive. This data string contains user’s unique user ID for our Web site. This technology also allows Emirates Identity to customize user experiences when it visits the Federal Authority for Identity and Citizenship Web site.

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Emirates ID Authority is not responsible for the privacy practices of any other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

### Surveys

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose any information. The information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as age level). Contact information will be used to notification of results. Other information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

### Security

This website takes possible precaution to protect information gathered. When users submit information via the website, this information is protected both online and off-line. In certain areas, we use encryption to protect sensitive information online; we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information of the clients. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to inquiry@emiratesid.ae (USE SECURITY HELP DESK EMAIL)

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage, so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

### Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, please email to [info@emiratesid.ae](mailto:info@emiratesid.ae) (USE PORTAL HELP DESK EMAIL)
